{
    "lvl1" :[
        {
            "question": "Finish the declaration for the main method: ",
            "snippet": "public static ____ main(String [] args)",
            "answer": "void",
            "id": 1   
        },
        {
            "question": "Finish the code to print out the message on a new line: ",
            "snippet": "System.out._______('Hello World')",
            "answer": "println",
            "id": 2   
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the parameter for this code?",
            "snippet": "public string garden(peach){",
            "answer": "peach",
            "id": 3   
        },
        {
            "question": "Declare a character variable with the name letter",
            "answer": "char letter",
            "id": 4   
        },
        {
            "question": "Declare a float variable with the name peanut",
            "answer": "float peanut",
            "id": 5   
        },
        {
            "question": "What kind of variable allows a lot of characters?",
            "answer": "string",
            "id": 6   
        },
        {
            "question": "Declare a string variable named sentence",
            "answer": "String sentence",
            "id": 7   
        },
        {
            "question": "Declare a class named House",
            "answer": "Class House",
            "id": 8   
        },{
            "question": "Declare an array of integers named id",
            "answer": "int [] id",
            "id": 9   
        },{
            "question": "Finish the code to print out the message on the same line ",
            "snippet": "System.out._______('Hello World')",
            "answer": "print",
            "id": 10   
        }
    ]
}